So I've just got back from Dubai.
My Porsche is in the shop.
I'm tired, I'm jet-lagged,
and today I'm in the Audi.
This is the RS Q8 Performance,
they call it the poor man's Urus.
Oh,
you couldn't afford the Lamborghini Urus.
That could be true, but the thing is,
I've got four cars.
I've got a Porsche Cayenne in the UK,
which is for my mom
and dad. I've got this,
I've got the Golf R, and the 911 GT3.
And do you know what? If it
was just the car for me,
maybe I'd have the Urus,
maybe I'd have the GT3 RS. But either way,
we're not here for
semantics, we're here to talk business.
I've spent a lot of time talking to a lot
of business owners in Dubai, and I
cannot believe so many of them
are making the same grave mistake.
But just before we get into that,
I'll show you where the Porsche is.
I suppose to me it just becomes a value
thing.
Is the Urus worth 200K more than the Audi
RS Q8 Performance? I don't think so.
Is the GT3 RS
worth 200K more than the GT3?
Because that's how much it bloody costs
over here
in Australia, mate. When it's worth it,
I'll pay for it. And do you know what?
I've got evidence of that.
Do you know what they are, brother?
It's Emirates first class slippers.
When it comes to travel,
is it worth the extra money to have a
shower on a plane? Yes.
We're here at Maxxine's Designs.
Let's have a look at the bloody Porsche
911, mate.
Also, I reckon this bad boy could actually
give the Urus a run for its money with how
it looks.
I thought I'd mix it up rather than always
just ranting on about business.
I was like,
"I'm going to bring people to have a look
at the car."
Any criminals in here
that can't be on camera?
It's fine. It's fine, yeah.
Oh. I'll blur her out in the edit.
[laughing]
It's looking good. I saw the wings
and I was like, "Oh,
I need to see it in real
life."
Looks pretty full on.
Stressing you out?
Nah, nothing stresses me out. I love it.
You know me.
Just keep bringing them up.
Let's keep going. What's the next board?
I don't know.
Hello.
Hello. You going to do the
floorboard, Corey? Yeah. Yeah. Do it,
yeah.
You're going to become famous.
Black ends are nice.
Was this as stressful as doing it in
white?
Probably more, to be honest.
Really, worse?
Yeah, there's a lot more goes into it.
I remember you saying
when you did the white one, you were like,
"That's a whole
day of your life just gone."
Yeah. Disappeared. Now I've lost a week.
That looks decent. Where's that going?
He's always trying to pick up on my
sneakiness.
[laughing] So if you see here.
No way.
Because that's all going to be black in
there, and then this part here, so
that's all going to be black.
Then this part here,
I'm going to do the in your
color.
That's insane.
So when you open the door,
all the color's there.
Adam Sullivan's going to be taking his
straight back to the guy who's done his-
Yeah
... and been moaning about it.
I told him to send it to you,
but he's too cheap to pay for the shipping
down to
the South Wales.
He couldn't afford you, could he?
[laughing]
Couldn't afford you.
Just never ask me what I've spent in wraps
this year.
But the good thing is,
all the branding for Nutonic's going on
that.
The reason I've got no voice
is because we've just launched Nutonic in
the UAE.
So you can now go to the website
and get Nutonic from that.
Australia formulation is coming,
it's just proving to be
a pain in the arse.
So there's some other pretty cool
changes thought up into the Porsche,
and I'm actually getting another
exhaust modification [laughs] in a couple
of weeks
because the car is there to market the
business.
It's got to be the best it can be.
Just going to reverse into my bloody car
parking
spot.
Absolutely classic. This
is supposed to be where you park the
Porsche.
Oh, dear, oh dear, oh dear.
So I tell you what, when I was in
Dubai,
there were quite a lot of creators
that I met whilst giving out Nutonic on
the stand. I was chatting to them. I
was like, "Oh yeah, got a business talk
tomorrow." And there was a few of them,
I said, "Can you make it?" They were like,
"Oh, no, sorry, I'm playing golf."
Or someone else was busy doing
something else. And they
were kind of asking a few questions.
The two ways that I always gauge how well
a business is doing are, I go, "Cool,
what's your follower size, and how big
is your email list?" Now, golden rule
is you should have 20% of your total
followers on your email list,
and so many people didn't have an email
list.
I was like, "What the..." One business
was making 25K a month,
didn't have an email
list,
and they couldn't fathom as to why it
was so important for their business.
And actually,
if you want to hear a wild story,
I went for lunch somewhere
where one of our main Nutonic investors
was for lunch.
So I made a point of going to his hotel
and buying him lunch,
and as I was buying him lunch,
we're in a nice restaurant,
I see Iman Gadzhi.
And some of you will see
that I've made videos about copying his
titles and
thumbnails. Went over
and I literally said to him, "Hey mate,
been copying some of
your titles and thumbnails. Thanks.
Keep up the good work." I get a message
from him two hours later, no idea how he
got my number,
and he invited me to this sauna ice bath
place
that was Russian on Sunday night,
and it was mental.
We met, we chat,
we spoke business for a bit,
then I had the shit kicked out of me
in a sauna, with branches.
They're whipping you with branches.
Then they put you into an ice bath,
and then this Russian man works like a
shaman,
swirling the ice and making you dunk
under.
It's the coldest I've ever been in my
life.
The Russians had to carry me out the ice
bath to put me back in the sauna.
I thought I was going to die.
But I tell you what,
a near-death experience, one
hell of a way to bond with someone.
There's going to be a link in the
description
to my free Lead Magnet Mastery course.
But let me show you why it's so important
to flipping
have an email list.
I thought my laptop was up here,
but it's not.
Babe,
do you not realize how much of an appeal
to authority you've diminished?
Babe, when people come in
and watch me doing videos,
they're not going to see
my 450K car in the background.
They're going to think I'm poor.
Do you want people to think I'm poor, Tay?
Well, you've already got an Audi RS Q8.
Now, all of you should be aware,
or maybe not, you probably don't care
that much, that I turned my business
mentorship offline. The reason I did
that was I'm just so flipping busy.
As you can tell, I'm fucked.
Just launched Nutonic in another country.
I'm fighting for my life out here.
But this month
Just from the business mentorship.
Been fully offline,
no business mentorship sales.
$102,000,
and I've only posted twice on this
business channel, which is
why I'm posting now. The only reason
that I've been able to make that amount of
money is through emails
and through running lead magnets in the
months before this.
I can't stress to you how important
sending emails is.
Now, my fitness business,
you probably would've noticed
that I've been spamming
people with more emails.
We're up 51% month on month.
Completely separate business.
All I've been doing
is sending emails because I've
been tired.
I've been stretched way too thin.
I've been overworking way too much.
So this month,
I took the month off Discord.
I've taken the month off creating content,
bar two videos.
And instead, all I put my focus in
is to send emails.
And for any of you wondering, "Oh,
how do I get emails?" That's why I've
created
the free Lead Magnet Mastery course below.
My manager, he does music events
and festivals and that.
He's done 50 Cent, Fisher, whatever,
and he will
know how many tickets he sold to
that event on the amount of emails he's
run and
got in the sign-ups. It's that simple.
Your business lives
and dies on the amount of emails
that you can get.
Met one guy at the weekend,
he had 800,000 YouTube subscribers and
5,000 emails. I said, "Brother, if you
drew that on a table,
the discrepancy would be massive.
Absolutely massive."
If you do not have 20%
of your total following on your email
list, you have not been collecting enough
emails.
And if you do,
you best start growing your bloody
following, mate.
You will live
in that balance forever because you
are going to burn out sometime
soon, like me,
and you're going to be fucked,
and you're going to be tired, and
you're going to be grumpy,
and you're going to be an asshole to be
around.
And then all you need to do
is not talk to camera, not
script videos, not spend time writing.
You just open your laptop,
and you just bang out an email.
It's what I've done, and my businesses
are up.
I just pretty much took a month off
"marketing," quote unquote, to
launch a podcast,
launch Nutonic in the UAE.
I still made cash. Not enough GT3 RS.
Listen, I wanted a manual, all right?
And the GT3 RS hasn't got the boot space
you need in the front.
So download that free Lead Magnet course,
or don't. I'm not your fucking dad.
And in the meantime,
if you feel like having a binge session,
YouTube reckons you should watch this
video here.
All right.
Fuck off.